const STORE = {
    questions: [//1
      {
        question: "What type of coffee would you get if you mix: 50% milk, 25% steamed milk, and 25% espresso?",
        options: [
          "Americano", 
          "Flat-White", 
          "Cappucino", 
          "Hot-Chocolate"
        ],
        answer: "Cappucino"
      },
      //2
      {
        question: "What type of coffee would you get if you only have espresso in your cup?",
        options: [
          "A cup",
          "A latte", 
          "A cup of Espresso",
          "This Question is too easy gimme something harder"
        ],
        answer: "A cup of Espresso"
      },
      //3
      {
        question: "What type of coffee would you get if you mix: 75% water, and 25% Espresso?",
        options: [
          "Black Coffee", 
          "Iced Coffee", 
          "I think the correct answer is actually Cappucino but that was the answer to question 1...", 
          "Americano"
        ],
        answer: "Americano"
      },
      //4
      {
        question: "What type of coffee would you get if you mix: 25% coffee, and 25% water?	", 
        options: [
          "Now i know for sure this is Black Coffee... i think",
          "Pumpkin spice",
          "Caffine",
          "Almond Milk Coffee",
        ],
        answer: "Now i know for sure this is Black Coffee... i think"
      },
      //5
      {
        question: "What type of coffee would you get if you mix: 75% steamed milk, and 25% espresso?",
        options: [
          "Esspresso", 
          "Hot milk", 
          "wait, is there such a thing as Hot milk coffee?", 
          "Cafe Latte"
        ],
        answer: "Cafe Latte"
      },
      //6
      {
        question: "What type of coffee would you get if you mix: 25% sugar, 25% espresso, 50% water?",
        options: [
          "Hot Coffee", 
          "Turkish Coffee", 
          "White Chocolate ", 
          "I dont think i will ever drink this type of coffee, like ever?"
        ],
        answer: "Turkish Coffee"
      },
      //7
      {
        question: "What type of coffee would you get if you mix: 50% Steamed milk, and 50% espresso?",
        options: [
          "Iced Coffee", 
          "like TBH this coffee has wayyy to much calcium", 
          "Flat White", 
          "Ameriano"
        ],
        answer: "Flat White"
      },
      //8
      {
        question: "What type of coffee would you get if you mix: 25% espresso, and 75% steamed milk?", 
        options: [
          "Did you know that if you substitute water with redbull and coffee, you get a flying college student", 
          "Pumpkin Spice Coffee", 
          "Latte Machiato", 
          "Carmel Machiato"
        ],
        answer: "Latte Machiato"
      },
      //9
      {
        question: "What type of coffee would you get if you mix: 25% whipped cream, 25% steamed milk, 25% espresso, and 25% chocolate syrup?",
        options: [
          "Cafe Machiato", 
          "Kurig Coffee", 
          "Carmel Mocha", 
          "roses are red, violets are blue, hint- this coffee is sweet, just like you ;P"
        ], 
        answer: "Cafe Machiato"
      },
      //10
      {
        question: "What type of coffee would you get if you mix: 100% coffee, and 100% Ice",
        options: [
          "Hot cup of coffee obviously", 
          "Iced Coffee", 
          "Did you know the most expensive cup of coffee ever sold was in San Francisco for $1,200?", 
          "British Coffee"
        ],
        answer: "Iced Coffee"
      },
    ],
    currentQuestion: 0,
    score: 0
  };